{
    "id": "55862942fee444858cb0bd790b21ef5b",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was so tired that she couldnâ€™t even stand ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6655e89439a4f458a96aac4107b94eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her parents are very conservative and stand ................................................ traditional family values.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7dd8486d29744f9b1bf9e1fc0f69c50"
        },
        {
            "question": "Now that John has fallen ill we should find someone else to stand ................................. for him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9fb917e16e7c45908d75f293f3f58349"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wants to stand ........................................ Parliament at the next election.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "237096b445e24dd5807c7079d8991564"
        },
        {
            "question": "Good friends will stand ........................................ you during both good and bad times.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e50485b5a13342dda8b39ec00dc53d40"
        },
        {
            "question": "A woman must stand ................................... her man.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c32fb3bd083040fa90a686433565bbd5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Marc was not the best candidate so it stands ................................... no reason that he got the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "92fed7e2a2f54a79aa5e748aa295bd5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Apple iPad had many features that made it stand ......................................... from other tablet computers on the market.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8bc35f00c7fc46078ef38ea616e16424"
        },
        {
            "question": "The chairman is standing ...................................... from his position because of ill-health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f9db8b901ff8466ab818fb9ccd07a32f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bold girl stood .......................................... the rowdy who tried to misbehave with her and slapped him right across his face.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "up",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ece5b2a684c3479fa10b799379ffc20f"
        }
    ]
}